Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XI: Houston Mayor, 1997-2004, 213482
  - Subseries C: Campaigns, 230936
    - Issues/Talking Points at Events, 1999; 234418 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Mailers, 1999; 234419 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Radio/TV Advertisements, 1999; 234420 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Re-election Campaign, 1999; 234421 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Re-election Campaign Polling, 1998-1999; 234422 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Schedule Requests, 1999; 234423 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Vargora, Craig, 1998-1999; 234424 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Voter Survey, 1999; 234425 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Ballot Application, 2001; 234426 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Bell, Chris, 2001; 234427 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Budget, 2001; 234428 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Calendar, 2001; 234429 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Campaign Expenses, 2002; 234430 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Campaign Materials, 2001; 234431 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Campaign Notes, 2001; 234432 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Constituents, 2001; 234433 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 2001; 234434 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Debates, 2001; 234435 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Election Day Talking Points, 2001; 234436 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Election Results, 2001; 234437 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Endorsements, 2001; 234438 (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Fundraising, 2001; 234439 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Hispanic Chamber, 2001; 234440 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Houston Police Department, 2001; 234441 (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - Interviews, 2001; 234442 (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - Issues/Talking Points at Events, 2001; 234443 (Box 56, Folder 48-49)
    - League of Women Voters, 2001; 234444 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Mailers, 2001; 234445 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Media Requests, 2001; 234446 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Minority Issues and Women, 2001; 234447 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Notes, 2001; 234448 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Other Houston Campaigns, 2001; 234449 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Phone Calls, 2001; 234450 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases, 2001; 234451 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Radio/TV Advertisements, 2001; 234452 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Sanchez, Orlando, 2001; 234453 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Sanchez, Orlando (Restricted), 1993-1994; 234454 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Steering Committee, 2001; 234455 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Talking Points, 2001; 234456 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Vargora, Craig, 2000; 234457 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Vargora, Craig, 2001; 234458 (Box 57, Folder 15-16)
    - Voter Returns, 2001; 234459 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Voting, 2001; 234460 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Website, 2001; 234461 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Subseries D: Speeches, 230937
    - Benefit for Gary Johnson, 1997-01-08; 234462 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Commemoration, 1997-01-20; 234463 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Speech, 1997-01; 234464 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - SW Communication Association, 1997-02-06; 234465 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Health Law Conference, 1997-02-07; 234466 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Houston Baytown Employees UNICEF Dinner, 1997-02-08; 234467 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Ashbury Memorial Church, 1997-02-23; 234468 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - IRS Black History Program, 1997-02-25; 234503 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Black History Month, 1997-02; 234504 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Career and Recovery Resources, 1997-03-02; 234505 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Missouri City Baptist Church Program, 1997-03-02; 234506 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Church of the Living God Temple, 1997-03-03; 234507 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Stump Speech, 1997-03-10; 234508 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Baptist Mission District Association of Texas, 1997-03-15; 234509 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - UH Law Center Gala, 1997-03-20; 234510 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Sheila Richard - Black History, 1997-03-26; 234511 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - Generic Speech, 1997-03; 234512 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - Leadership Houston - Prairie View A&M University, 1997-04-02; 234513 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - North Forest I.S.D., 1997-04-11; 234514 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - Asian American Officer of the Year (floppy disk), 1997-04-26; 234515 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Generic Church Speech, 1997-04; 234516 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - A Child Is Born, 1997-05-15; 234517 (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - Holman Street Baptist Church, 1997-05-16; 234518 (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - Community Partnership for Youth, 1997-05-17; 234519 (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - United Way Texas Gulf Coast, 1997-05-20; 234520 (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Sandra Robinson - Rice School, 1997-05-28; 234521 (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - Patterson Elementary Literature Magnet School, 1997-05-28; 234522 (Box 57, Folder 46)
    - Tanglewood Academy Graduation, 1997-05-30; 234523 (Box 57, Folder 47)
    - Milby Senior High School, 1997-05-31; 234524 (Box 57, Folder 48)
    - Announcement Speech, 1997-06-01; 234525 (Box 57, Folder 49)
    - Jesse H. Jones High School Commencement, 1997-06-01; 234526 (Box 57, Folder 50)
    - Brentwood Church, 1997-06-04; 234527 (Box 57, Folder 51)
    - Black Chemists and Chemical Engineers, 1997-06-13; 234528 (Box 57, Folder 52)
    - Cancer Counseling, Inc., 1997-06-16; 234529 (Box 57, Folder 53)
    - Employee Workplace - Drugs in the Workplace, 1997-06-19; 234530 (Box 57, Folder 54)
    - Toastmasters - HPD, 1997-06-22; 234531 (Box 57, Folder 55)
    - Seven Point Ethics Plan, 1997-06-25; 234532 (Box 57, Folder 56)
    - Post-Announcement Stump Speech, 1997-06-26; 234533 (Box 57, Folder 57)
    - Law Enforcement Training Center, 1997-06-27; 234534 (Box 57, Folder 58)
    - Southlawn Palms Apartments, 1997-06; 234535 (Box 57, Folder 59)
    - M.D. Anderson Cancer Center, 1997-07-12; 234536 (Box 57, Folder 60)
    - Varnett School Summer Youth Program, 1997-07-17; 234545 (Box 57, Folder 61)
    - Volunteers Meeting - Mayor Campaign, 1997-07-17; 234546 (Box 57, Folder 62)
    - Edwards Family Reunion, 1997-07-24; 234547 (Box 57, Folder 63)
    - Antioch Missionary Baptist Church, 1997-07-27; 234548 (Box 57, Folder 64)
    - Church of the Living God, 1997-07-29; 234549 (Box 57, Folder 65)
    - Green Grove Missionary Baptist Church, 1997-08-08; 234550 (Box 57, Folder 66)
    - Houston Chamber of Commerce - Mayoral Debate, 1997-08-26; 234551 (Box 57, Folder 67)
    - Tarrant County Black Bar Association, 1997-09-12; 234553 (Box 57, Folder 68)
    - New Community Baptist Church, 1997-09; 234554 (Box 57, Folder 69)
    - So La Ti Village, 1997-10-04; 234556 (Box 57, Folder 70)
    - Acres Home Citizens Council, 1997-10-25; 234557 (Box 57, Folder 71)
    - Trinity United Methodist Church, 1997-10-26; 234558 (Box 57, Folder 72)
    - Texas State Beauty League, 1997-10; 234559 (Box 57, Folder 73)
    - Election Night Remarks, 1997-11-03; 234561 (Box 57, Folder 74)
    - Christian Women of Distinction, 1997-11-14; 234562 (Box 57, Folder 75)
    - Al Gore Introduction, 1997-11-24; 234563 (Box 57, Folder 76)
    - Anti-Crime Strategy, 1997-11-28; 234564 (Box 57, Folder 77)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1997-11; 234566 (Box 57, Folder 78)
    - Victory Speech Draft, 1997-12-06; 234567 (Box 57, Folder 79)
    - New Orleans Chamber, 1997-12-19; 234568 (Box 57, Folder 80)
    - "Confronting the Issues of Change", 1997; 234572 (Box 57, Folder 81)
    - Fragements, 1997; 234573 (Box 57, Folder 82)
    - Speeches by CMNEAL Enterprises, 1997; 234575 (Box 57, Folder 83)
    - Inaugural Address, 1998-01-02; 234576 (Box 57, Folder 84)
    - Byrd - Graham Amendment Unvieling, 1998-01-19; 234577 (Box 57, Folder 85)
    - "C" Club Annual Reception, 1998-01-20; 234579 (Box 57, Folder 86)
    - State of the City Address, 1998-01-20; 234580 (Box 57, Folder 87)
    - Read Commission, 1998-01-22; 234582 (Box 57, Folder 88)
    - Youth Summit, 1998-02-04; 234583 (Box 57, Folder 89)
    - Jerusalem Missionary Baptist Church, 1998-02-15; 234585 (Box 57, Folder 90)
    - South-Asian Chamber of Commerce Event, 1998-02-19; 234586 (Box 57, Folder 91)
    - Mt. Sinai Baptist Church, 1999-02-22; 234589 (Box 57, Folder 92)
    - National Urban League Press Conference, 1998-02-26; 234590 (Box 57, Folder 93)
    - Speech, 1998-03-03; 234623 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - FAA Aviation Forecast Conference, 1998-03-24; 234624 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Greater Houston Restaurant Association, 1998-03-24; 234625 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Alumni College Luncheon - Rice University, 1998-03-28; 234636 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - President Clinton's Visit to Houston, 1998-04-08; 234637 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - President Clinton's Visit to Johnson Space Center, 1998-04-14; 234638 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - New Lobbying Ordinance Press Conference, 1998-04-15; 234652 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - San Antonio's Bid for the 2007 Pan Am Games, 1998-04-15; 234666 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - BFI/Junior Achievement Graduation, 1998-04-22; 234667 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Clean Neighborhood Program, 1998-04-22; 234668 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Houston Community College - 1st Annual Literacy Summit, 1998-04-22; 234669 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Commissioner El Franco Lee Reception, 1998-04-23; 234670 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Houston Housing Finance Corporation Press Conference, 1998-04-23; 234671 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - North Forest ISD Recognition Program, 1998-04-23; 234672 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - American Leadership Forum Luncheon, 1998-04-24; 234673 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Fire Station 72 Grand Opening, 1998-04-24; 234674 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Credit Rating Agency Meeting, 1998-04-27; 234675 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - BAHR Annual Meeting, 1998-04-30; 234676 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Israel National Day Reception, 1998-04-30; 234677 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Tribute to Imam Ibrahim Kamalud-din, 1998-05-01; 234678 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Arab American Cultural and Community Center, 1998-05-02; 234679 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - LULAC Cinco de Mayo Parade, 1998-05-02; 234680 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Asian-American Heritage Month, 1998-05-03; 234681 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Older Americans Day, 1998-05-03; 234682 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Texas Businesswoman's Awards, 1998-05-03; 234683 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Ministerial Advisory Board, 1998-05-04; 234684 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - City Attorney Press Conference, 1998-05-05; 234685 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - HISD Employer Appreciation Luncheon, 1998-05-05; 234686 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Sesquicentennial Park II Donor Party, 1998-05-06; 234687 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - National Conference, 1998-05-07; 234688 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Women Professionals in Government, 1998-05-07; 234689 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Public Relations Society, 1998-05-14; 234690 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Houston Police Memorial Service, 1998-05-15; 234691 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - TSU Law School Graduation, 1998-05-15; 234692 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - First Executive Forum, 1998-05-28; 234693 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Fire Cadet Graduation, 1998-05-29; 234694 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Holland Middle School Graduation, 1998-05-28; 234695 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Asian Banker's Luncheon, 1998-05-29; 234696 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Special Olympics Texas Press Conference, 1998-05-29; 234697 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - The High School for Law Enforcement Graduation, 1998-05-30; 234698 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Ross Sterling High School Graduation, 1998-05-30; 234699 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - Barbara Jordan Hgh School Graduation, 1998-05-31; 234700 (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - CPAL Conference, 1998-06-01; 234701 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - South Asian Community Reception, 1998-06-03; 234702 (Box 58, Folder 44)
    - ITT Technical Institute Graduation, 1998-06-06; 234703 (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - The Worship Center Service, 1998-06-07; 234704 (Box 58, Folder 46)
    - Lakewood Church Pastors and Leaders Conference, 1998-06-08; 234705 (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - Channel 11 Summer Safety Town Hall Meeting, 1998-06-09; 234706 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - Announcement of Affirmative Action Director, 1998-06-11; 234707 (Box 58, Folder 49)
    - Asian Business Organizations, 1998-06-11; 234708 (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Downtown District Groundbreaking Texas Avenue Project, 1998-06-11; 234709 (Box 58, Folder 51)
    - Fundraiser for State Representative Senfronia Thompson, 1998-06-11; 234710 (Box 58, Folder 52)
    - Houston Association of Realtors, 1998-06-11; 234711 (Box 58, Folder 53)
    - The Dewalt Center, 1998-06-12; 234712 (Box 58, Folder 54)
    - Grand Opening Ceremony for American First National Bank, 1998-06-12; 234713 (Box 58, Folder 55)
    - Houston Lesbian Gay Pride Celebration Kick-Off Party, 1998-06-12; 234714 (Box 58, Folder 56)
    - Independence Day Ball - 100th Anniversary of the Republic of the Phillipines, 1998-06-12; 234715 (Box 58, Folder 57)
    - Houston Area Urban League's 30th Anniversary Gala, 1998-06-13; 234716 (Box 58, Folder 58)
    - MCI Library "Link" Program Press Conference, 1998-06-13; 234717 (Box 58, Folder 59)
    - Welcoming Remarks for Namad, 1998-06-13; 234718 (Box 58, Folder 60)
    - 1998 Jimmy Carter Work Project, 1998-06-14; 234719 (Box 58, Folder 61)
    - Gethsemane Missionary Baptist Church, 1998-06-14; 234720 (Box 58, Folder 62)
    - Houston Habitat for Humanity, 1998-06-14; 234721 (Box 58, Folder 63)
    - Downtown/Midtown Transit Streets Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1998-06-15; 234722 (Box 58, Folder 64)
    - Reception Honoring Philip Carroll, 1998-06-17; 234723 (Box 58, Folder 65)
    - Houston Habitat for Humanity Reception, 1998-06-18; 234724 (Box 58, Folder 66)
    - NALEO Reception, 1998-06-18; 234725 (Box 58, Folder 67)
    - Non-Stop Air Service between Houston and Brazil Testimony, 1998-06-18; 234726 (Box 58, Folder 68)
    - Urban Litter Partnership, 1998-06-18; 234727 (Box 58, Folder 69)
    - Urban Litter Program, 1998-06-19; 234728 (Box 58, Folder 70)
    - 21st Century Community Learning Centers Press Conference, 1998-06-23; 234729 (Box 58, Folder 71)
    - Budget and C.I.P. Talking Points, 1998-06-24; 234730 (Box 58, Folder 72)
    - Regional Air Quality Summit Luncheon, 1998-06-24; 234731 (Box 58, Folder 73)
    - Regional Air Quality Summit Opening, 1998-06-24; 234732 (Box 58, Folder 74)
    - TMO Leaders Meeting, 1998-06-24; 234733 (Box 58, Folder 75)
    - Human Rights Campaign and Houston Federal Club, 1998-06-25; 234734 (Box 58, Folder 76)
    - NAACP Houston Branch Unity Awards, 1998-06-25; 234735 (Box 58, Folder 77)
    - State Democratic Convention in San Antonio, 1998-06-27; 234736 (Box 58, Folder 78)
    - Corinthian Point Residential Subdivision Groundbreaking, 1998-06-28; 234737 (Box 58, Folder 79)
    - FUUSA Rescue Youth Center, 1998-06-28; 234738 (Box 58, Folder 80)
    - Mt. Heron Baptist Church, 1998-06-28; 234739 (Box 58, Folder 81)
    - I-69 - NAFTA Superhighway Summit, 1998-06-29; 234740 (Box 58, Folder 82)
    - Luncheon with Hon. Ehud Olmert, Mayor of Jerusalem, 1998-06-29; 234741 (Box 58, Folder 83)
    - Summer Youth Program Kick-Off, 1998-06-29; 234742 (Box 58, Folder 84)
    - Democratic Convention, 1998-06; 234743 (Box 58, Folder 85)
    - HPD Civilian Review Committee Reception, 1998-07-07; 234744 (Box 58, Folder 86)
    - Houston-Galveston National Youth Leadership on Medicine, 1998-07-07; 234745 (Box 58, Folder 87)
    - International Jazz Festival, 1998-07-07; 234746 (Box 58, Folder 88)
    - Operation Sell-Out, 1998-07-07; 234747 (Box 58, Folder 89)
    - Texas American Planning Association, 1998-07-07; 234748 (Box 58, Folder 90)
    - Alief Community Association, 1998-08-01; 234749 (Box 58, Folder 91)
    - Middle East Trip Talking Points, 1998-08-04; 234750 (Box 58, Folder 92)
    - Messiah Communications, 1998-08-07; 234751 (Box 58, Folder 93)
    - Prairie View University Graduation, 1998-08-08; 234752 (Box 58, Folder 94)
    - Central Housing Annual Meeting, 1998-08-10; 234753 (Box 58, Folder 95)
    - Greater Houston Convention and Visitors Bureau Meeting, 1998-08-13; 234754 (Box 58, Folder 96)
    - Hispanic Housing Education Corporation, 1998-08-17; 234755 (Box 58, Folder 97)
    - Stop the Violence Billboard Kick-Off, 1998-08-17; 234756 (Box 58, Folder 98)
    - "C" Club Luncheon, 1998-08-18; 234757 (Box 58, Folder 99)
    - D.A.R.E. Press Conference, 1998-08-26; 234758 (Box 58, Folder 100)
    - Dr. Martin Luther King Dedication Ceremony, 1998-08-28; 234759 (Box 58, Folder 101)
    - Houston Renaissance, 1998-08-31; 234760 (Box 58, Folder 102)
    - Nieghborhoods Connection Conference, 1998-09-12; 234761 (Box 58, Folder 103)
    - Asian-Houstonians Honoring the Mayor, 1998-09-20; 234762 (Box 58, Folder 104)
    - Port of Houston Authority AAPAC Convention, 1998-10-06; 234763 (Box 58, Folder 105)
    - Houston Contractors Association Luncheon, 1998-10-22; 234764 (Box 58, Folder 106)
    - Serve Houston Youth Corps, 1998-10-30; 234765 (Box 58, Folder 107)
    - 25th Anniversary Celebraion of Sikh Center, 1998-11-02; 234766 (Box 58, Folder 108)
    - Jesse Jones Centennial Celebration, 1998-11-10; 234767 (Box 58, Folder 109)
    - Taxi Dancing Press Conference, 1998-11-13; 234768 (Box 58, Folder 110)
    - Acres Homes CDC Groundbreaking, 1998; 234769 (Box 58, Folder 111)
    - Children's Assessment Center, 1998; 234772 (Box 58, Folder 112)
    - Crime Stoppers Annual Meeting, 1998; 234773 (Box 58, Folder 113)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1998; 234774 (Box 58, Folder 114)
    - Hispanic Appointees, 1998; 234775 (Box 58, Folder 115)
    - Houston Grand Opera - Pre-Performance Dinner, 1998; 234777 (Box 58, Folder 116)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police, 1998; 234778 (Box 58, Folder 117)
    - Mayor Bob Lanier, 1998; 234780 (Box 58, Folder 118)
    - METRO Appointments, 1998; 234782 (Box 58, Folder 119)
    - NAACP Unity Awards, 1998; 234784 (Box 58, Folder 120)
    - NALEO Conference, 1998; 234785 (Box 58, Folder 121)
    - Neighborhood Protection Department, 1998; 234786 (Box 58, Folder 122)
    - NFL Commissioner Paul Tagliabue, Owners Committee Chair Jerry Richardson, and NFL Staff, 1998; 234788 (Box 58, Folder 123)
    - NFL News Conference, 1998; 234789 (Box 58, Folder 124)
    - Nominations, 1998; 234791 (Box 58, Folder 125)
    - Public Service Recognition Week, 1998; 248996 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Speech research, 1998; 248997 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - University of St. Thomas - "Celebrate the Positive", 1998; 248998 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Urban League Luncheon, 1998; 248999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors, 1998; 249000 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Williamson/Kessler Board Book Center Dedication, 1998; 249001 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Senator Rodney Ellis, Gerald Smith, and Milton Carroll Meeting, 1999-01-05; 249002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Appointment of Barbara Chelette to Fire Department Command Staff, 1999-01-06; 249003 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Taiwanese Chamber of Commerce, 1999-01-06; 249004 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Northeast Ministers Alliance Meeting, 1999-01-07; 249005 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Rhapsodies in Black: Art of the Harlem Renaissance visit, 1999-01-07; 249006 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - After School Bicycle Safety Project, 1999-01-08; 249007 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Channel 2 Editorial Meeting, 1999-01-11; 249008 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - METRO Press Conference, 1999-01-11; 249009 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - International Business Expo, 1999-01-13; 249010 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Northeast Surface Water Purification Plant, 1999-01-13; 249011 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Junior Achievement Exchange City Dedication, 1999-01-14; 249012 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Main Street Corridor Meeting, 1999-01-14; 249013 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Texas Society of CPAs, 1999-01-14; 249014 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Town Hall Meeting, 1999-01-14; 249015 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Houston 2000 Transporation Plan, 1999-01-15; 249016 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Oratorical Contest Honoring Martin Luther King, Jr., 1999-01-15; 249017 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Rice University - Leadership Skill Development Program, 1999-01-15; 249018 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Doicese of Galveston, 1999-01-17; 249019 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - North Main Church of God in Christ Community Fellowship, 1999-01-17; 249020 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Black Heritage Society, 1999-01-18; 249021 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Antioch Baptist Church, 1999-01-18; 249022 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Honey Brown Hope Foundation, 1999-01-18; 249023 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - North Houston Frontiers Club, 1999-01-18; 249024 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - State of the City Address, 1999-01-19; 249025 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Continental Airlines Houston - Tokyo Route, 1999-01-20; 249026 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Texas Business Network Meeting, 1999-01-20; 249027 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Drug Seizure Press Conference, 1999-01-21; 249028 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Executive Forum Luncheon, 1999-01-21; 249029 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Task Force 2000 PAC/WIN PAC, 1999-01-21; 249030 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Texas Chinese TV Interview, 1999-01-21; 249031 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - National Forum for Black Public Administrators, 1999-01-22; 249032 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Shell Youth Training Academy, 1999-01-22; 249033 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Spring Business Press Conference, 1999-01-22; 249034 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Transportation Press Conference, 1999-01-22; 249035 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - India Culture Center - Republic Day of India Celebration, 1999-01-24; 249036 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Attracting Capital to Africa Summit Press Conference, 1999-01-25; 249037 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Consul General Wu Zu Rong Reception, 1999-01-25; 249038 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Joe Weikerth Roast and Toast, 1999-01-25; 249039 (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - After-Council Presentation - New Motorized Podium, 1999-01-26; 249040 (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Clean Air Press Conference, 1999-01-26; 249041 (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Houston Livestock Show and Rodeo, 1999-01-26; 249042 (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - Mayor's Literary Leadership Award, 1999-01-26; 249043 (Box 59, Folder 48)
    - Funeral Services for Pastor John Osteen, 1999-01-27; 249044 (Box 59, Folder 49)
    - Leadership 20/20 Breakfast, 1999-01-27; 249045 (Box 59, Folder 50)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, 1999-02-07; 249046 (Box 59, Folder 51)
    - Combined Municipal Campaign Recognition, 1999-02-16; 249047 (Box 59, Folder 52)
    - Leadership 20/20 Meeting, 1999-02-17; 249048 (Box 59, Folder 53)
    - Senator Slade Gordon Fundraiser, 1999-02-18; 249049 (Box 59, Folder 54)
    - Airport Terminal AB Garage Construction Groundbreaking, 1999-02-19; 249050 (Box 59, Folder 55)
    - Building Management Improvement Press Conference, 1999-02-19; 249051 (Box 59, Folder 56)
    - Interfaith Prayer Breakfast and Fellowship, 1999-02-20; 249052 (Box 59, Folder 57)
    - Jerusalem Missionary Baptist Church, 1999-02-21; 249053 (Box 59, Folder 58)
    - Asian Trip Press Briefing, 1999-02-22; 249054 (Box 59, Folder 59)
    - Fox Channel 26 Morning News, 1999-02-22; 249055 (Box 59, Folder 60)
    - Redesign Main Street Press Conference, 1999-02-22; 249056 (Box 59, Folder 61)
    - Anti-Defamation League SW Regional Board Meeting, 1999-02-23; 249057 (Box 59, Folder 62)
    - Gulf Meadows Civic Club Meeting, 1999-02-23; 249058 (Box 59, Folder 63)
    - Questions about 3rd Floor Carpet Talking Points, 1999-02-24; 249059 (Box 59, Folder 64)
    - Tax Abatement Program, 1999-02-24; 249060 (Box 59, Folder 65)
    - Asia One Radio/Asian Trip Press Briefing, 1999-02-25; 249061 (Box 59, Folder 66)
    - Austin High School Visit, 1999-02-25; 249062 (Box 59, Folder 67)
    - Gumbeaux Magazine, 1999-02-26; 249063 (Box 59, Folder 68)
    - Astronaut Eugene Cernan Press Conference, 1999-03-01; 249064 (Box 59, Folder 69)
    - Salute to the Red Cross, 1999-03-01; 249065 (Box 59, Folder 70)
    - Houston Bar Association Annual Leon Jaworski Award Luncheon, 1999-03-02; 249066 (Box 59, Folder 71)